newfunapp.com 2013-01-15

# newfunapp.com Terms and Conditions

**Date Last Modified:**

This Privacy Policy was last modified December 27, 2012

We are dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our users. This Privacy Policy describes the ways we collect, store, use, and manage the information you provide in connection with our website or any Social application provided on our websites or other third party sources (collectively, the "Services").

By using the Services, you are agreeing to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are responsible for periodically reading this Privacy Policy. If you use our Services after we have updated this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that you have read the updated terms and consent to our revised privacy practices. Use of the Services after changes are made to the Privacy Policy will be considered your consent to the new terms.

**Information Collected and Used :**

The information we collect is used to improve the content and the quality of our Services, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for any purposes, except to provide products or services you've requested.

When you access the Services we will ask for extended and special permissions from your Facebook account if it is necessary for the application. The permissions must be accepted in order to use the application. Please note that because third parties manage the purchases of virtual goods offered by the Services, we do not have access to your credit card details and billing information.

In short we only collect that information that requires for the social application that you want to use. And most important that we are not sharing user's information in any situation or condition.

**Advertising :**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of our Ad Partners for more detailed information about their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or web sites. We only use approved Facebook advertising providers that have strict rules: 

**Data Storage :**

We are using third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Services. And they are providing best online security as we know. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy :**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important for us. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access our website at any time or in any manner. If we learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the our Site then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information immediately.

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents or guardians for permission before sending any personal information to anyone over the Internet.

**Contact Information:**

If you need any help or want to report anything(bad content, problem with the game, copyright issue, privacy policy) : Please E-Mail to **cvora064@gmail.com** we are happy to serve you at our best.
